Nathan S Jang

Software Engineer

Permanent Resident of U.S.

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with a background in the Michelin starred culinary scene for over 8 years. I am a self starter who is a reliable and responsible individual, having experience in high pressure and fast paced working environments, successfully producing finest quality end results. I have a strong passion for learning, maintaining, and improving complex systems.

PROJECTS

KUSAKABE (github) — React, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose

Make an online order MERN stack app for famous Omakase restaurant named 'KUSAKABE' using React, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Material UI

Calculator (github) — React, Codesandbox

During the React hackathon, built a simple calculator with other developers using React and Codesandbox

Nathan's recipe blog (github) — MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Google-OAuth, Material Design

Make recipe sites from my experience using MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Google-OAuth and Material design for styling

Minesweeper (github) — HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Simple Minesweeper Game using HTML, CSS, Java Script

EXPERIENCE

The Shota, San Francisco, CA — Sushi & Kitchen Chef

MAR 2019 - MAR 2020

Trained and supervised new staff members as well as managing and leading the team. Ensure highest quality and timely delivery of course of the meal.

Kusakabe, San Francisco, CA — Sushi & Kitchen Chef

OCT 2016 - MAR 2019

Being promoted after 3 months of learning, served as a sushi & kitchen chef in an Omakase (Chef's Prix Fixe Menu) restaurant serving Sushi-in-Kaiseki style. Successfully led the team in a face paced and a high pressured environment.

Walnut Creek, CA 94597 (415) 317-5944 nathan.s.jang@gmail.com https://grey1287.github.io/Portfolio/ linkedin.com/in/nathan-sb-j github.com/NathanSJang

SKILLS

Languages

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Python

Databases and Frameworks

React | Express | MongoDB | Mongoose | Material design

Tools

Figma | Trello

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive San Francisco, CA

12 weeks of full-time coding bootcamp in Software Engineering program running from October 2020 to February 2021

Recognized and voted as "The most elegant coder"

California Culinary Academy

Culinary ArtsSan Francisco, CA

LANGUAGES

English, Korean